Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/sangnguyen-099480140 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Research
Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)
React.js

Sang Nguyen

Software Engineer at Grab Vietnam

Summary

I love math and algorithms. I am consistently intrigued by new technologies especially Web and AI or Machine Learning. It is said that "Life's greatest difficulties always happen right before life's greatest breakthroughs". Consequently, I am not afraid of researching many kinds of modern techniques to improve myself perfectly. My career path is to become a full-stack website developer.

Experience

Grab
Software Engineer
February 2022 - Present (3 years 2 months)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

ZALORA Group Software Engineer September 2021 - January 2022 (5 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Zalo
2 years 2 months
Software Engineer
October 2020 - August 2021 (11 months)

Associate Software Engineer July 2019 - September 2020 (1 year 3 months) Ho Chi Minh

Mainly working on ZaloPC

Harvey Nash Vietnam
Front End Developer
April 2018 - April 2019 (1 year 1 month)

Zalo

Associate Software Engineer March 2018 - April 2018 (2 months) Ho Chi Minh

Trường Đại Học Khoa Học Tự Nhiên Studying September 2013 - February 2018 (4 years 6 months)

Education

VNUHCM - University of Science
Bachelor's degree, Information Technology